Simon Fraser Student Society fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Simon Fraser Student Society fonds
1964 - 2009
F-74
Q106642919
4.32 m of textual records ca. 250 photographs ca. 200 posters
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION Photographs are found only in series 8 (Clubs and affiliated groups), sub-series 3 (Outdoor club); see sub-series description for file locations. Posters comprise all of series 12 (Publications), sub-series 4 (Posters).
Simon Fraser Student Society
The Simon Fraser University Society (SFUSS) was established on October 5, 1965. "University" was later dropped and it is now known as the Simon Fraser Student Society (SFSS). The SFSS still maintains its original constitutional objectives: "to promote, direct, administer, coordinate all student activities of, by and for the students of Simon Fraser University, and to promote cooperation amongst the students of Simon Fraser University and cooperation between the members of the Society and students within the Province and elsewhere." Its mandate has come to include advocating for students rights and providing services to graduate and undergraduate members. These include advocacy services, such as Legal Aid and Women's Centre, and retail services, such as Quad Books, the Print Shop and the Pub.
In its first year, the Society organized social events, co-sponsored Vietnam teach-ins, started a co-op bookstore, and protested against the poor quality food offered on campus. In the 1970s, the Society organized against tuition fee increases, lobbied for improved on-campus housing, started a women's centre, and opened a student-run pub. The 1980s saw the development of plans for a student union building and a continuation in the struggle for affordable education. In the 1990s the Society has constructed the Maggie Benston Centre, expanded its services and continues to advocate on behalf of students for accessible, affordable education.
The Executive Council originally consisted of 14 elected officers: President, Vice President, Secretary, Treasurer, Ombudsman, Clubs Director, Public Relations Officer, Arts, Science and Education Presidents, Athletics Coordinator, Social Convenor, Cultural Director, and Housing coordinator. This remained until 1977 when changes to constitutional by laws established five at large positions: President, Treasurer, External and Internal Relations Officers, Secretary, and Public Relations Officer and the Ombuds Office. Currently, six elected Executive officers and 36 Student Union representatives elected by students from each academic department sit on the Forum, the student representative body responsible for all major Student Society decisions. The Departmental Student Unions and Standing Committees supply information and recommendations to the Forum. Student Society Standing Committees deal with every aspect of the Society's operations.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the organization.
Fonds consists of records created, received, and collected by the Simon Fraser Student Society and its affiliated groups on campus in the course of administration of student government and business. Included are records relating to the Constitution, minutes of Executive meetings, the Executive, finance and budgets, campus committees, elections, student unions, clubs and affiliated groups, publications, subject files, and audio material.
The arrangement of the records into series was established by the archivist to reflect the main functions and activities of the Society. Note that two series numbers are no longer in use:
Series 9 (Publications) was replaced by series 12 (Publications) when the archivist re-organized its contents into sub-series.
Series 11 (Audio recordings) was discontinued in 2008 when the Archives deaccessioned its contents (recordings of Society meetings).
Photographic materials; Graphic materials; Textual records; Community life
The fonds was donated by the Simon Fraser Student Society.
All accessions have been processed as of June 2006. Further accruals are expected.
See also F-17, The Peak Publications Society fonds; The Peak is SFU's student newspaper funded by the SFSS. The Archives also holds the records of the Simon Fraser University Women's Centre, a constituency group of the SFSS; see fonds F-40.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as stipulated by Archives policy or the donor. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
Series descriptions and file lists are available.
- Constitution, 1964 - 1984; F-74-1; 12 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of the constitution of the Simon Fraser Student Society. Included are the first constitution, proposed amendments, Constitution Committee reports, incorporation of student societies, reference material on student government and by-laws.
  - Background material on student government, 1964 - 1966; F-74-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
    Textual records
    Open
  - Constitution, 1966 - 1969; F-74-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1966; F-74-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
    Pending review
  - Constitution, 1967; F-74-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1968; F-74-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1969; F-74-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1971; F-74-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1973; F-74-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1977; F-74-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1981; F-74-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Constitution, 1984; F-74-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
- Minutes, 1965 - 1991; F-74-2; 1.28 m of textual records
  Series consists of minutes of meetings of the executive council of the Simon Fraser Student Society together with agenda, papers, and relevant correspondence. Records reflect a wide range of issues affecting the student body at Simon Fraser, such as the PSA Strike, and the day to day operation of the Student Society. Also covered are budget allocations and student clubs.
  - Listing of Student Society Minutes, 1965 - 1980; F-74-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1965; F-74-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1966; F-74-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1966; F-74-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1966; F-74-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1966; F-74-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes re: The Peak, 1966; F-74-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1967; F-74-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1967; F-74-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1967; F-74-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-2)
  - Minutes, 1967; F-74-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1968; F-74-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1968; F-74-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1968; F-74-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1969; F-74-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1969; F-74-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1969; F-74-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1969; F-74-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1970; F-74-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1970; F-74-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
    Restricted in part
  - Minutes, 1970; F-74-2-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1971; F-74-2-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1971; F-74-2-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1971; F-74-2-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 74-3)
  - Minutes, 1972; F-74-2-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1972; F-74-2-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1972; F-74-2-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1973; F-74-2-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1973; F-74-2-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1973; F-74-2-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1974; F-74-2-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1974; F-74-2-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1974; F-74-2-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1975; F-74-2-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1975; F-74-2-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1975; F-74-2-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 74-4)
  - Minutes, 1976; F-74-2-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1976; F-74-2-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1976; F-74-2-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1977; F-74-2-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1977; F-74-2-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1977; F-74-2-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1978; F-74-2-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1978; F-74-2-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes (incomplete), 1978; F-74-2-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1979; F-74-2-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1980; F-74-2-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1980; F-74-2-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 74-5)
  - Minutes, 1981; F-74-2-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 74-6)
  - Minutes, 1981; F-74-2-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 74-6)
  - Minutes, 1981; F-74-2-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 74-6)
  - Minutes, 1981; F-74-2-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 74-6)
  - Minutes, 1981; F-74-2-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 74-6)
  - Minutes, 1981; F-74-2-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 74-6)
  - Mindex, Unofficial Indexed Minutes, 1981 - 1982; F-74-2-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 74-7)
  - Minutes, 1982; F-74-2-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 74-7)
  - Minutes, 1982; F-74-2-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 74-7)
  - Minutes, 1982; F-74-2-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 74-7)
  - Minutes, 1982; F-74-2-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 74-7)
  - Minutes, 1982; F-74-2-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 74-7)
  - Minutes, 1982; F-74-2-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 74-7)
  - Minutes, 1983; F-74-2-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1983; F-74-2-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1983; F-74-2-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1983; F-74-2-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1983; F-74-2-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1983; F-74-2-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1984; F-74-2-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1984; F-74-2-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1984; F-74-2-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1984; F-74-2-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1984; F-74-2-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 74-8)
  - Minutes, 1984; F-74-2-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, Annual General Meeting, 1984; F-74-2-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1985; F-74-2-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1985; F-74-2-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1985; F-74-2-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1985; F-74-2-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1985; F-74-2-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1985; F-74-2-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1986; F-74-2-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1986; F-74-2-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1986; F-74-2-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 74-9)
  - Minutes, 1986; F-74-2-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1986; F-74-2-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1986; F-74-2-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1986; F-74-2-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1987; F-74-2-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1987; F-74-2-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1987; F-74-2-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1987; F-74-2-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1987; F-74-2-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1987; F-74-2-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1987; F-74-2-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1988; F-74-2-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1988; F-74-2-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 74-10)
  - Minutes, 1988; F-74-2-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1988; F-74-2-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1989; F-74-2-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1989; F-74-2-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1989; F-74-2-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1989; F-74-2-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1989; F-74-2-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1989; F-74-2-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1990; F-74-2-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1990; F-74-2-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1990; F-74-2-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 74-11)
  - Minutes, 1990; F-74-2-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
  - Minutes, 1991; F-74-2-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
  - Minutes, 1991; F-74-2-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
- Executive, 1965 - 1989; F-74-3; 90 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence and related records of the Executive Council. Included are records reflecting issues of the day, and the general scope of activities of the members of the Executive Council.
  - Executive Council, 1965 - 1984; F-74-3-1; 11 cm of textual records
    - Executive lists, 1965 - 1984; F-74-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
    - Correspondence, 1965; F-74-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 1971; F-74-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
    - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-12)
    - Correspondence, 1969; F-74-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - Correspondence, 1971; F-74-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
  - President, 1965 - 1971; F-74-3-2; 38 cm of textual records
    For a list of President's represented in the correspondence, see Access Points.
    Buzan, Tony; Mynott, John; Turner, Alex; Wong, Stan; Rudelier, Nelson; Hicks, Greg; Weeks, Arthur; Loney, Martin; Dumphries, Chris; Walsh, Robert R.; Wickstrom, Norman; Doherty, Peter
    - Tony Buzan - Correspondence, 1965; F-74-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - Tony Buzan - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - Tony Buzan - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - Alex Turner - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - Alex Turner - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - John Mynott - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - John Mynott - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - John Mynott - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - John Mynott - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - Stan Wong - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-13)
    - Stan Wong - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Stan Wong - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Stan Wong - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Nelson Rudelier - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
      Restricted in whole
    - Greg Hicks - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Arthur Weeks - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
      Open, no restrictions
      File reviewed for access (Oct 2023): no restricted information identified.
    - Arthur Weeks - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Arthur Weeks - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Arthur Weeks - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Martin Loney - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Rob Walsh - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 74-14)
    - Rob Walsh - Correspondence 1/2, 1969; F-74-3-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Rob Walsh - Correspondence 2/2, 1969; F-74-3-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Chris Dumphries - Correspondence (In), 1969; F-74-3-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Chris Dumphries - Correspondence (Out), 1969; F-74-3-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Norm Wickstrom - Correspondence (In), 1969; F-74-3-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Norm Wickstrom - Correspondence (Out), 1969; F-74-3-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Norm Wickstrom - Correspondence (In), 1970; F-74-3-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Norm Wickstrom - Correspondence (Out), 1970; F-74-3-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 74-15)
    - Norm Wickstrom - Correspondence (In) [file missing], 1970; F-74-3-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - Peter Doherty - Correspondence (Out), 1970; F-74-3-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - Norm Wickstrom - Correspondence (In), 1970; F-74-3-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - Norm Wickstrom - Correspondence (In), 1971; F-74-3-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
  - Vice-president, 1965 - 1970; F-74-3-3; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1966; F-74-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - 1st Vice President - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - 1st Vice President - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - 1st Vice President - Correspondence, 1970; F-74-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - 2nd Vice President - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - 2nd Vice President - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - 2nd Vice President - Correspondence, 1969 - 1970; F-74-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
  - Secretary, 1966 - 1970; F-74-3-4; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 1968; F-74-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - Correspondence, 1970; F-74-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
  - Treasurer, 1965 - 1970; F-74-3-5; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1967; F-74-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
    - Correspondence, 1969 - 1970; F-74-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-16)
  - Business Manger, 1965 - 1969; F-74-3-6; 4 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1966; F-74-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1968 - 1969; F-74-3-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
  - Club Director, 1965 - 1970; F-74-3-7; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1968; F-74-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1969 - 1970; F-74-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
  - Cultural Director, 1965 - 1966; F-74-3-8; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1966; F-74-3-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
  - Inter-house Coordinator, 1965 - 1967; F-74-3-9; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1967; F-74-3-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
  - Activities Coordinator, 1967 - 1971; F-74-3-10; 7 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1969; F-74-3-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-17)
    - Correspondence, 1969; F-74-3-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence 1/2, 1970; F-74-3-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence 2/2, 1970; F-74-3-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence, 1971; F-74-3-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Public Relations Officer, 1965 - 1970; F-74-3-11; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1966; F-74-3-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence, 1967; F-74-3-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence, 1968 - 1970; F-74-3-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Social Convener, 1966 - 1967; F-74-3-12; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 1967; F-74-3-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Sports Coordinator, 1966 - 1967; F-74-3-13; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 1967; F-74-3-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Arts President, 1967 - 1969; F-74-3-14; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1967 - 1969; F-74-3-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence, 1968; F-74-3-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Education President, 1965 - 1970; F-74-3-15; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1965 - 1969; F-74-3-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-15-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence, 1968 - 1970; F-74-3-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Science President, 1966 - 1969; F-74-3-16; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 1969; F-74-3-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
    - Correspondence, 1967 - 1968; F-74-3-16-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Councilor-at-Large, 1967 - 1968; F-74-3-17; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1967 - 1968; F-74-3-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-18)
  - Ombudsman, 1965 - 1989; F-74-3-18; 6 cm of textual records
    Simon Fraser Student Society. Ombuds Office
    - Correspondence, 1965; F-74-3-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
    - Correspondence, 1966; F-74-3-18-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
    - Correspondence, 1967 - 1968; F-74-3-18-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
    - Correspondence, 1969 - 1970; F-74-3-18-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
    - Annual report, 1983 - 1985; F-74-3-18-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
    - Annual report, 1985 - 1989; F-74-3-18-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
    - Ephemera, 1986; F-74-3-18-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
  - Student Senators, 1967 - 1974; F-74-3-19; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1967 - 1974; F-74-3-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
- Finance, 1966 - 1989; F-74-4; 18 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the financial responsibilities of the organization. Included are Executive budgets, club budgets, expense vouchers, Auditors' Reports, and financial statements.
  - Budgets, 1966; F-74-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
  - Budgets, 1966; F-74-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
  - Preliminary Budgets, 1966; F-74-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-19)
  - Budgets 1/2, 1966; F-74-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-19)